https://www.inhouseblog.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - InhouseBlogAboutPost HereSubscribeAdvertisePost a JobFind a Job InhouseBlogIn-house Counsel Jobs and News Since 2005 CareersIn-House Counsel JobsGeneral Counsel JobsLegal Recruiter ListInhouse Counsel GuidesGC Directory
MUST READ
December 11, 2019 | Inhouse Counsel Salaries – 2020 Guide
May 27, 2018 | In-House Counsel Jobs – Corporate Counsel Jobs
April 26, 2018 | Legal Recruiter Directory
April 3, 2018 | General Counsel Jobs
February 22, 2018 | How to Get an In-House Counsel Job
August 14, 2014 | The In-House Counsel Resume – Get Traction with Your In-House Search
January 27, 2014 | Acing the In-House Interview
January 13, 2014 | The Ideal In-House Candidate
Search for:
Privacy PolicyWelcome to our InhouseBlog.com website (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by Law Department Solutions, LLC (“LDS”, “our”, “us” or “we”). By using the Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us using the information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.  By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy and any other agreement that we might have with you. If you do not agree with any of the terms and conditions of this policy, do not use the Site.Information We Automatically CollectWe automatically collect certain information to help us understand how our users use our Site, including a user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, the pages a user has visited, the date and time of visits, a user’s location, browser type and operating system type (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as “Usage Data”). In addition, we collect Usage Data using technologies called “cookies” and “web beacons”. A cookie is a piece of data or text file on your computer that identifies you as a unique user. A web beacon is an object that is embedded in a page or e-mail and is usually invisible to the user but allows checking that a user has viewed the page or e-mail. We use cookies and/or web beacons for a number of purposes, including to improve the quality of the Site and to make the Site easier to use. We may combine Usage Data with Personal Information (as defined below) in a manner that enables us to trace Usage Data to an individual user, and may collect, use, preserve and disclose Usage Data in any manner that we may collect, use, preserve and disclose Personal Information as provided herein (whether Usage Data is combined with any Personal Information or otherwise).As more particularly described below in this Privacy Policy, we use certain third party tools and services to assist us in collecting Usage Data. Such tools and services include Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Certain of the third party tools and services, such as Google Analytics, use “cookies” or “web beacons” to help analyze how users use the Site. Google Analytics uses “cookies” which collect anonymous traffic data. We do not access or control these third party “cookies” or “web beacons”, however, we may have access to data generated from their use, such as when we view analytics reports provided by such third party tools and services.Information You Choose To Submit We collect information about you that you choose to submit to us in connection with your use of the Site.  For example, if you subscribe to our newsletter we may collect your name, email address and other information about you and your organization. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” is information that specifically identifies an individual, whether alone or when combined with Usage Data and “Non-Personal Information” is information that does not specifically identify an individual.Disclosure and UseExcept as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information to any third party unless the third party is a Permitted Recipient. You agree that we may disclose your Personal Information to the following “Permitted Recipients”: (1) persons or entities that you permit to access or receive your Personal Information (your permission being reasonably determined from your actions in view of the circumstances), (2) providers of services to LDS such as an Internet hosting provider, Internet services provider, email distribution and email management providers, and software development or maintenance providers, provided that we have a reasonable belief that such providers will maintain your Personal Information in confidence, (3) to third parties that provide services enabling us to market and advertise the Site, other LDS goods and services and other content that has been customized for you through targeted advertising, targeted content and other means, and (4) any other person or entity to whom we are permitted to disclose your Personal Information by law or other provision of this Privacy Policy.We also may disclose Personal Information to third parties in a manner that does not identify a particular individual. For example, and not by way of limitation, we may disclose aggregated Personal Information to marketing and research partners and/or for advertising, marketing and promotional purposes.We may use your Personal Information for a variety of purposes. For example, we may use your Personal Information to provide, maintain and improve the Site and our services, including the information we provide to you via the Site. If you are a subscriber to our email newsletters, we may also use your Personal Information to contact you, such as to notify you of changes to the Site and our services, to conduct research, to resolve disputes and to solicit your feedback and input about the Site and our services. All emails sent to users by the Site other than our general email newsletters are transactional emails about your use of the Site and not promotional in nature.As noted above, we may collect, use, preserve and disclose Usage Data in any manner that we may collect, use, preserve and disclose Personal Information (whether Usage Data is combined with such Personal Information or otherwise).Other Authorized DisclosuresNotwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, you understand and agree that LDS may collect, use, preserve and disclose any information (including, without limitation, Usage Data and Personal Information): (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or when otherwise required by law, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims in LDS’ sole discretion, (2) to protect the rights and property of LDS or the public, including the enforcement of this Privacy Policy and any other agreement we may have with you or your organization (as applicable), (3) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding unauthorized distribution of another’s intellectual property or information, illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person (provided, however, that we have no obligation to do so), or (4) that is available to the general public.LDS may, from time to time, assign or transfer all or a portion of the Usage Data and/or Personal Information and its rights and obligations hereunder to one or more third parties (whether in connection with a sale of assets, a merger or otherwise), in which case the successor or assignee will agree to abide by the obligations under this Privacy Policy with respect to the Usage Data and Personal Information transferred to such successor or assignee (unless otherwise agreed to by you and such successor or assignee).Any information shared by you with us may be shared with or transferred to any LDS affiliated entity or third party provider (including those located outside the European Union), no matter where located, for the purpose of providing you services and improving the Site. By using the Site, you consent to this transfer and acknowledge that the services provided to you and the functionality of the Site could not be provided without such a transfer. If you do not wish your information to be transferred in this way do not use the Site.In addition to the other uses and disclosures of information set forth in this Privacy Policy, and notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may use, disclose, assign and transfer for any purpose, any Non-Personal Information.SecurityLDS and its providers employ certain procedural and technological security measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your Personal Information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. None of such measures, or any data transmission over the Internet or any network, can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure or effective. As a result, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or that is submitted on your behalf, and such information is transmitted and submitted at your own risk.You agree to keep your Personal Information private and confidential, and not to share information and materials that you receive by or through the Site with any third party other than through the general, non-commercial methods permitted by the Site.  For example, the Site permits you to share links to content through a sharing tool available on certain pages of the Site.Third Party Sites, Resources, Tools, Services and Widgets; Advertisements, Sponsorships and PromotionsThe Site may link to other websites (including, without limitation, employer and recruiter websites) and Internet resources, or incorporate third party tools, services and widgets, that are not owned, operated or controlled by LDS. In addition, the Site may contain advertisements, sponsorships and promotions of third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that may be collected from you by (a) such other websites and Internet resources or by any of such third parties in connection with such advertisements, sponsorships and promotions, or (b) any such third party tools, services and widgets. You should be aware, however, that providers of third party tools, services and widgets, and advertisements, sponsorships and promotions on the Site may utilize “cookies”, “web beacons” and other mechanisms to collect information from you about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to, among other things, provide additional functionality, advertisements, sponsorships and promotions about information, products or services that may be of interest to you. LDS is not responsible for any (i) information, products or services available on or through any linked sites or resources, or through any such advertisements, sponsorships and promotions, (ii) third party tools, services or widgets, or (iii) third party terms of use, privacy policies or information collection, use and disclosure practices. We recommend that you review all of terms and use and privacy policies provided by the applicable third parties.Ability to AcceptBy using the Site, you affirm that you are competent to accept, and have accepted, the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.ChangesThis Privacy Policy may be modified at any time and for any reason and without notice to you, other than the posting of the modified Privacy Policy at the Site. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices. You agree to check back and review this Privacy Policy periodically and agree that you are bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy, as may be modified from time to time. If we are going to use Personal Information collected through the Site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, then we will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on the Site for 30 days prior to such use or by other means as required or permitted by law.MiscellaneousThe terms “such as,”, “include”, “including”, “for example,” “e.g.,” or any variation thereof means “including the following by way of example only, without limitation” and shall not be construed to limit any general statement that it follows to the specific or similar items or matters immediately following it.Your California Privacy RightsUnder California Civil Code sections 1798.83, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information (as defined therein) we share with third parties for those third parties direct marketing purposes. California residents who would like a copy of this notice or who have questions or concerns about our privacy practices and policies may contact us at info@lawdepartmentsolutions.com or write to us at Law Department Solutions, LLC, ATTN: Privacy Coordinator, 83 Morris Street, Suite 2, New Brunswick, NJ 08901. In your request, please specify that you want a “Your California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response.Additional QuestionsAgain, feel free to contact us any time if you have further questions about the Site. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at info@lawdepartmentsolutions.com with the word “Privacy” in the subject line. Alternatively, you can write to us at Law Department Solutions, LLC, ATTN: Privacy Coordinator, 83 Morris Street, Suite 2, New Brunswick, NJ 08901. * Like this? Click here to get our weekly email featuring in-house news, jobs and announcements *In-house Counsel JobsPost an In-House Job at GoInhouse®Get In-House Counsel Job AlertsGeneral Counsel JobsFeatured In-House Counsel JobsLegal Recruiter DirectoryPopular PostskFetch – Contract Research Made Easy (Adv.)Visit kFetch.com today to research contracts for free!Other Sites to Visit ABA JournalAssociation of Corporate CounselLaw Department Management BlogGeoffrey G. Gussis, Esq. (Editor) (c) 2005-2020 Law Department Solutions, LLC. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy |
InhouseBlog® and GoInhouse® are our registered trademarks.All other trademarks are property of their respective owners.
